<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xt:extensions xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension/extensions.xsd">
    <xt:extension id="teilex0-oxygen-framework">
        <xt:location href="teilex0-oxygen-framework.zip"/>
        <xt:version>1.2.0</xt:version>
        <xt:oxy_version>14.0+</xt:oxy_version>
        <xt:type>framework</xt:type>
        <xt:author>Boris Lehečka</xt:author>
        <xt:name>TEI Lex-0 Tools</xt:name>
        <xt:description xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
         <html>
          <head>
           <title>Java Classes Generator</title>
          </head>
          <body>
         <h3>TEI Lex-0 Tools, version 1.2.0</h3>
         <p>Tools for eiditing, transforming and analyzing dictionaries in <a href="https://bit.ly/tei-lex-0">TEI Lex-0</a> format in oXygen XML Editor.</p>
         <p>Supported version of TEI Lex-0:</p>
         <ul>
          <li>0.9.1</li>
          <li>0.9.0</li>
         </ul>
         <p>Tools</p>
         <ul>
          <li>templates</li>
          <li>inserting entry with basic structure</li>
          <li>separate view of the body with entries</li>
          <li>separate view of the teiHeader</li>
          <li>extraction of the list of the headwords</li>
          <li>statistics of used elements and attributes</li>
          <li>export to PDF</li>
         </ul>
         <h3>History</h3>
         <h4>1.2.0</h4>
         <ul>
          <li>advanced styling with CSS</li>
          <li>alternative CSS for inline senses</li>
          <li>statistics form <strong>&lt;gram&gt;</strong> elements</li>
         </ul>
         <h4>1.1.0</h4>
         <ul>
          <li>path to the transformation scenarios changed</li>
          <li>default transformation scenarios removed</li>
         </ul>
        </body>
        </html>
        </xt:description>
        <xt:license>
<![CDATA[

END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT

MIT 2.0


Copyright 2023 DARIAH-ERIC Working Group Lexical Resources. All rights reserved.
          
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without 
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
  *    Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, 
       this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
  *    Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, 
       this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation 
       and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
        
 This software is provided by the copyright holders and contributors
 "as is" and any express or implied warranties, including, but not
 limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for
 a particular purpose are disclaimed. In no event shall the copyright
 holder or contributors be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental,
 special, exemplary, or consequential damages (including, but not
 limited to, procurement of substitute goods or services; loss of use,
 data, or profits; or business interruption) however caused and on any
 theory of liability, whether in contract, strict liability, or tort
 (including negligence or otherwise) arising in any way out of the use
 of this software, even if advised of the possibility of such
 damage.

]]></xt:license>
    </xt:extension>
</xt:extensions>